okay hello welcome everybody this is JDK
好的，你好，欢迎大家，这是JDK
9 the hidden gems
9隐藏的宝石
I'm Michael vid stet until recently I
我是Michael vid stet，直到最近我
used to be a JVM tech guy and then I
曾经是JVM技术人员，然后我
moved to the dark side and I'm out now
搬到黑暗的一面，我现在不在
managing the DBM but hopefully I will
管理DBM，但希望我会
stay technically enough for this to be
保持足够的技术性
interesting
有趣
hi I'm sandy sonatine senior software
您好，我是Sandy Sonatine高级软件
engineer and technically Intel and we
工程师和技术上与我们
work with Oracle and the open JDK
与Oracle和开放式JDK合作
community to optimize Java for Intel
社区为英特尔优化Java
platforms cool so we'll be talking about
平台很酷，所以我们将讨论
hidden gems in data k9 this is the
数据k9中的隐藏宝石是
Oracle version of the slide that says
幻灯片的Oracle版本说
that everything I'm about to say is a
我要说的都是
lie I believe that Sonia will have her
撒谎，我相信索尼娅会拥有她
corresponding slide at the end of the
末尾的相应幻灯片
slide deck so stay tuned for that
滑盖，敬请期待
this being a presentation on JDK 9 at
这是在JDK 9上的演示
JavaOne shortly after we launched
我们推出不久后的JavaOne
galvanize clearly is two dimension
镀锌明显是二维的
jigsaw there's no way around that right
拼图没有办法解决这个问题
so in theory this could be a
所以从理论上讲，这可能是
presentation of data on jigsaw
拼图上的数据展示
specifically so all the great stuff
特别是所有很棒的东西
we've done to modularize the JDK the
我们已经完成了对JDK的模块化
cool tools we built to improve on that
我们为改善这一点而打造的出色工具
so you can create your custom theories
因此您可以创建自定义理论
you can start out with this module graph
您可以从此模块图开始
that we have in the JDK you can
我们在JDK中可以
streamline that and only include the
精简并仅包括
modules that you actually need for your
您实际需要的模块
job application I could talk about how
我可以谈论工作申请
you end up with runtimes they are very
您最终会遇到运行时
much smaller
小多了
I could also touch on support we've
我也可以谈谈我们的支持
added to have multi release jar files
添加有多个版本的jar文件
and in a way make sure that you can run
并以某种方式确保您可以运行
your job application no matter which JDK
您的工作申请，无论使用哪个JDK
you're running on and stream seamlessly
您正在运行并无缝播放
a lot of people to do that and I can
很多人这样做，我可以
also touch on support we have added to
也可以参考我们添加到的支持
Java C to make that even easier so that
Java C使之更加容易
you can compile for certain JDK release
您可以为某些JDK版本进行编译
these are all jigsaw related things so
这些都是拼图相关的东西
we're not going to talk about that this
我们不会谈论这个
is the hidden gems of JDK 9 we're going
是我们要去的JDK 9的隐藏宝石
to try to touch on the other stuff that
尝试去探讨其他东西
has gone into data k9 so all the small
已经进入数据k9，所以所有小
things that tend to sort of end up in
往往倾向于最终的事情
the shadow in the shade behind dat
dat后面阴影中的阴影
canine jigsaw I'm gonna start dawn by
犬拼图，我要开始黎明
touching on tools and libraries quickly
快速接触工具和库
I'm gonna say something about hotspot
我要谈谈热点
and JVM and Sanjay is gonna touch a lot
JVM和Sanjay将会碰到很多
on the performance improvements we've
关于我们的性能改进
done
完成
if you go to the JDK 9 page you'll see
如果转到JDK 9页面，您将看到
something along the lines of what's on
发生了什么事
the right-hand side here so we have you
右边在这里，所以我们有你
know some schedule and a bunch of
知道一些时间表和一堆
features that we've added that we worked
我们添加的功能可以正常工作
on and it doesn't look much until we
继续，直到我们
realize that the page is significantly
意识到页面很重要
longer than that thank you are rarely oh
比那更长的时间谢谢你很少哦
by the way for this slide and the
顺便说一下这张幻灯片和
animation I don't have the management
我没有管理的动画
skill sets yet to create it myself but
自己创造技能的技能，但是
if you want to go look at what's in JDK
如果您想看一下JDK中的内容
9 you can do exactly this you can go to
9您可以完全做到这一点，可以去
the JDK 9 page and have a look hopefully
JDK 9页面，并希望有一个外观
you'll get some inspiration from this
你会从中得到一些启发
presentation and when I count the depths
演讲以及我计算深度时
we have on this page I ended up with
我们在此页面上最终得到了
something
某事
jep's are our JDK enhancement proposals
jep是我们的JDK增强建议
therefore relatively large features are
因此相对较大的功能是
very visible or things that are very big
非常明显或很大的东西
impact or large features and in many
影响或大型功能
cases its large features so in JDK 9 we
它具有很大的功能，因此在JDK 9中我们
have 90 really big features this is just
有90个真正的大功能，这仅仅是
counting the Japs on top of that we have
最重要的是，
all the other improvements so this is a
所有其他改进，所以这是一个
big release for us it contains a lot of
对我们来说是一个很大的发布，它包含很多
different things and again if we're
不同的事情，如果我们是
gonna touch on a few of them in this
在这方面要涉及其中的一些
presentation so starting with the the
演示，所以从
the tools and libraries one thing we
工具和库我们一件事
have added and I don't think that's not
添加了，我不认为这不是
anything like no presentation of the
就像没有介绍
other one here is complete without at
另一个在这里完整，没有
least it touching on Jay shell because
至少它碰到杰伊壳，因为
it's such a cool tool so other runtimes
这是一个很酷的工具，所以其他运行时
have had support for rebel based playing
曾经支持基于叛乱的游戏
around with code for quite some time and
在很长一段时间内都使用代码
now it's the turn has come to Java so
现在轮到Java了，所以
Jay shell is a read eval print loop tool
周杰伦壳牌是一个读评估打印循环工具
that you can use to try out things try
你可以用来尝试的东西尝试
out code and experiment with things
出代码并尝试一些东西
without having to create your Java class
无需创建Java类
file and use Java C to compile it and
文件并使用Java C进行编译并
deploy it and all of that so I'm running
部署它以及所有这些，以便我运行
Jay shell here hopefully you can see
周杰伦壳牌希望你能看到
well maybe not the leftmost couple of
好吧，也许不是最左边的几个
pixels but at least GHL you can do
像素，但至少可以做到GHL
obviously simple things like adding a
显然很简单的事情，例如添加
couple of numbers why not assign a
几个数字为什么不分配一个
variable and why not say you know take
变量，为什么不说你知道
that variable and add four these are all
该变量并加上四个，这些都是
sort of standard simple things you
某种标准的简单事物
should recognize most of them
应该认识其中的大多数
that's J shell in itself but J shell
那是J Shell本身，但J Shell
also has other cool functionalities I'm
还有其他很酷的功能
gonna actually demo another thing that
实际上会演示另一件事
we have added in jdk 9 the first thing
我们在jdk 9中添加了第一件事
I'm gonna do is to say list ov and then
我要说的是ov，然后
I'm gonna tab and J shell actually has
我要标签和J Shell实际上有
support for printing out the Java Docs
支持打印Java文档
for methods it has tab completion and
对于方法，它具有制表符补全和
and can also print out the Java Docs you
并且还可以打印出您的Java文档
can get help in the J shell tool itself
可以在J Shell工具本身中获得帮助
in case you're not sure what parameters
如果您不确定什么参数
the function takes method takes I should
功能需要方法我应该
say in this case it may be a bit you
说在这种情况下可能会有点
know mysterious when you look at this
看着这个就知道神秘
but what I'm gonna say next is that
但是我接下来要说的是
we've added a func a piece of
我们在其中添加了一个func
functionality called convenience methods
称为便捷方法的功能
for collection convenience methods for
用于收集的便利方法
collections Factory whatever I have a
我有什么收藏工厂
set of functions methods that make it
一组使其成为函数的方法
easier to create collections with a
轻松创建收藏集
smallish number of elements so you can't
元素数量少，所以您不能
use this to create collections with a
使用它来创建带有
hundred elements but you can use it for
一百个元素，但您可以将其用于
single element or up to eight or so ten
单个元素或最多八个或十个
in this case I guess and the nice part
在这种情况下，我猜也是不错的部分
about these things is obviously takes
这些事情显然是需要的
less typing what you'd normally have to
减少通常需要输入的内容
do is to first create your list and then
首先要做的是创建您的列表，然后
go add and add and then you can start
去添加并添加，然后您可以开始
using the collection yeah with this you
使用这个集合耶
can instead create a list of let's say
可以创建一个清单，例如
I'm gonna have three elements to this
我要有三个要素
list and all of a sudden I have a list
清单，突然间我有了清单
of three elements what you can't see
看不见的三个要素
here I I guess I could force it but the
在这里我想我可以强迫它，但是
collection here is actually immutable
这里的收藏实际上是一成不变的
it's it's non-modifiable so you get back
这是不可修改的，所以你回来了
something that is read-only you can't
只读的东西你不能
actually add elements to it you can't
实际向其中添加元素
remove elements to it and there are some
删除它的元素，有一些
nice parts to that that we can leverage
我们可以利用的好地方
inside of the JDK in the JVM to optimize
在JVM中的JDK内部进行优化
the implementation of this collection so
该集合的实现如此
if we for example find a better way of
例如，如果我们找到更好的方法
representing the data here in the
代表这里的数据
background without the the full-blown
没有成熟的背景
collection that we'd otherwise have to
否则我们必须收集的
allocate to potentially support you
分配以潜在地支持您
adding an element later or removing an
以后添加元素或删除
element ATAR we can optimize something
元素ATAR我们可以优化一些东西
that is targeted for exactly one element
仅针对一种元素
without any modifications to it and that
对此没有任何修改
that does can help a lot with footprint
确实可以在足迹方面有很大帮助
but also with the performance
还有表现
that's another example I guess I could
那是另一个例子，我想我可以
create some we all love strings I'm
创建一些我们都喜欢我的弦
gonna create a hello world list here and
要在这里创建一个hello world列表，
then just because I like streams from
只是因为我喜欢来自
Java 8 I'm gonna say for each system
Java 8我要针对每个系统说
print line and you'll have your your
打印线，您将拥有自己的
string piece top or obviously I what I
弦片顶部或显然我什么我
also can do is put this together
也可以做到这一点
collectors meaning and you will have
收藏家的意思，你将有
your food hello world string another
你的食物你好世界串起另一个
piece of functionality with additive
附加功能
streams while I want we're on the topic
当我希望我们关注这个话题时
is a take wild operator so you can say
是一个疯狂的运算符，所以你可以说
for example that pick elements from this
例如从中挑选元素
dream while this thing is true or well
做梦，而这件事是正确的
the thing isn't true I guess so I'm
我猜这不是真的，所以我
gonna say while this the component here
要说的是这里的组件
doesn't equal comma and I'm gonna
不等于逗号，我要
collect that again
再次收集
and you one will get the hello there's
你会得到你好
also a drop dropped while so two new
也下降一滴，所以两个新
methods armed streams we like streams we
方法武装的流我们喜欢流我们
like optimizing streams and we've
例如优化流，我们已经
optimized streams of Arden JDK nine as
Arden JDK的优化流九为
well so improvements have gone in in
好，所以改进进来了
that general area
那个一般区域
speaking of concatenating strings and I
谈到串联字符串，我
couldn't find a good way of showing this
找不到显示此内容的好方法
because it's very sort of low level and
因为这是一个很低的水平
back-end ish in nature but one of the
后端ish本质上是其中之一
things we've done is to change the way
我们要做的事情就是改变方式
we generate bytecode for concatenating
我们生成用于连接的字节码
strings so for piecing strings together
字符串，以便将字符串拼接在一起
in the path so first of all there's a
在路径上，所以首先有一个
lot of string manipulation in Java so
Java中的很多字符串操作
it's very important for us to get that
这对于我们来说非常重要
right and optimize it correctly and in
正确并对其进行优化
the past what we had was a series of
过去我们拥有一系列
concatenation append operations that the
串联附加操作
the JVM and the JIT compiler had to sort
JVM和JIT编译器必须排序
of trying to pattern match and scrape
尝试图案匹配和刮擦
out and piece together in order to make
拼凑在一起，使
sense of the fact that in the end is
最终的事实是
just concatenating two strings what Java
只是连接两个字符串什么Java
C does starting with nine is to output a
C确实从九开始就是输出一个
bytecode sequence that is much more
字节码序列，还有更多
obvious for us to work with it's making
对我们来说显而易见的是
use of the invokedynamic instruction
使用invokedynamic指令
which is an instruction we added very
这是我们增加的一条指令
recently in the first and only
最近在第一个也是唯一的
instruction that has been added to Java
已添加到Java中的指令
and it's using this instruction to to
它正在使用此指令来
make it easier for the JVM to detect
使JVM更容易检测
this the other nice part about it is
这另一个好的部分是
that that same pattern it can week or
那个相同的模式可以一周或
more of the implementation and the
更多的实施和
optimization opportunities or then moved
优化机会，然后搬家
into the libraries so if in the future
进入图书馆，以便将来
release of the JDK we find a better way
JDK发行，我们找到了更好的方法
of optimizing this we have that same
优化这一点，我们有相同的
pattern we can detect it and again the
模式，我们可以检测到它，然后再次
update the implementation of
更新执行
concatenating the strings in the
连接字符串中的
background and you will all get the
背景，你们都会
benefits of that without having to
的好处而不必
change your code and so back to the
更改您的代码，然后回到
presentation I walked through J shell
我经历了J Shell的演示文稿
I've touched on convenience factory
我碰到了便利工厂
methods for collections that was the
收集方法是
order of the words I was looking for and
我要寻找的单词的顺序
in the five string concatenation which
在五个字符串的连接中
is again the concatenation of strings I
再次是字符串的串联
had backup slides in case the demo
有备用幻灯片，以防演示
didn't work out
没有解决
if you want to know more about J shell
如果您想进一步了解J shell
there are plenty of sessions during Java
Java期间有很多会议
one I recommend that you go to at least
我建议你至少去
one because J shell is extremely
一是因为J shell非常
powerful I have a slide at the end where
功能强大，我在末尾有一张幻灯片
if you if you forget about what was on
如果您忘记了发生了什么
that slide
那张幻灯片
moving into the VM one of the key things
进入虚拟机的关键之一
we've done on the JVM side is to switch
我们在JVM端所做的是切换
the default garbage collector it used to
过去的默认垃圾收集器
be the parallel garbage collector but we
成为并行垃圾收集器，但是我们
have now switched over to use g1 our
现在已经切换为使用g1
garbage first garbage collector as the
垃圾首先作为垃圾收集器
default the g1 garbage collector has as
默认情况下，g1垃圾收集器具有
its goal to provide both good throughput
其目标是提供良好的吞吐量
and low latency or low cost times it is
低延迟或低成本时间
region based so the way this works in
基于区域，因此它的工作方式
the background is that the whole heap is
背景是整个堆都是
split up into individual regions and
分成各个区域
then it's the g1 collectors choose very
那是g1收藏家选择的
carefully which regions it's going to
小心要去哪个地区
try to evacuate to empty and and clean
尽量疏散到空旷而干净的地方
up so that we can later reuse that for
以便我们以后可以重用
new allocations and basically the way it
新分配及其基本方式
works is that it picks the ones that
起作用的是，它选择了那些
have the most garbage first where the
首先拥有最多的垃圾
fewest objects are actually live still
最少的物体实际上仍然静止
and then it removes all those live
然后将所有直播者删除
objects out to somewhere else and what
反对其他地方，什么
you have in after that is obviously a
你在那之后显然是一个
clean empty region that you can start
清理可以开始的空白区域
allocating in so their name comes from
分配，以便他们的名字来自
the fact that it's taking the garbage
垃圾的事实
first as if you know the regions with
首先，好像您知道
the most garbage first the default post
最垃圾优先默认帖子
time target for g1 is 200 milliseconds
g1的时间目标是200毫秒
but this can be tilled so if you want
但这可以耕种，所以如果你想
more throughput for example and can
例如更高的吞吐量，并且可以
tolerate more post times
容忍更多的发布时间
then you can continue it one way or if
那么您可以以一种方式继续
you want low post times but you can
您希望缩短发布时间，但可以
tolerate and throughput overhead
容忍和吞吐量开销
I think it's unit the other way and as I
我认为这是另一种方式，就像我一样
mentioned g1 has been in the JDK for a
提到的g1已经在JDK中
while it's been made before now and we
虽然它是在现在之前制成的，但我们
have made some improvements to the
已经对
implementation of do you want to make it
你想实现的实现
more performant this is an ongoing
性能更高，这是一个持续的过程
effort so as a matter of fact if you
实际上，如果您
would pick up JDK 10 take the code today
会拿起JDK 10今天的代码
and compile it you would find that we
编译它，您会发现我们
have already improved on what's in 9 so
已经改进了9中的功能
there are a lot there's a lot of
有很多很多
activity going on here and
活动在这里进行
of improvements but the end goal here is
的改进，但最终目标是
really to have AGC in the default DC be
真的在默认DC中有AGC
one that that doesn't only care about
一个不仅仅在乎的
throughput but also takes low latency
吞吐量，但延迟时间短
into account and we believe that a lot
考虑到这一点，我们相信很多
of applications going forward will be in
的应用程序将在
one way or another latency-sensitive
一种方式或另一种时延敏感的
it's not just bulk processing of data if
不只是批量处理数据，如果
you want to know more about
您想了解更多有关
jg1 there are at least a couple of
jg1至少有几个
sessions that will touch on that so
会议将涉及到
again recommend you to go to those on
再次推荐你去那些
the topic of GCS one of the other things
GCS的主题之一是其他
we've done is to deprecate and remove
我们要做的是弃用并删除
some of the the code we have in the JVM
我们在JVM中拥有的一些代码
specifically we have deprecated the
具体来说，我们已弃用
concurrent mark-sweep collector the the
并发标记扫描收集器
CMS were short the CMS collector CMS has
CMS是CMS收集器CMS的简称
traditionally been used in low latency
传统上用于低延迟
use cases where you don't have very
用例你没有非常
large heaps and where your application
大堆以及您的应用程序在哪里
is relatively well behaved if I put it
如果我把它表现得比较好
that way the challenge for us on the JVM
这样，对我们在JVM上的挑战
side has been that the code base the
方面一直是代码库
implementation of the collector has been
收集器的实施已经
very very hard to maintain and it has
非常非常难以维护，它具有
been very hard to evolve the other
很难发展另一个
collectors while still making sure that
收藏家同时还要确保
CMS works the way it does so what we've
CMS的工作方式与我们所做的一样
done now is to deprecated it the goal is
现在要做的就是弃用它，目标是
to remove this in a future release we
在将来的版本中删除它
haven't decided which one yet and the
还没有决定哪一个
hope and goal here is to have the other
希望和目标是要有另一个
collectors fill the void device if you
收集器会填充空白设备，如果您
so will there will be cases where you
所以在某些情况下
may have to tune things differently for
可能需要针对不同情况进行调整
example and all that so if you're using
示例以及所有这些，如果您使用的是
CMS again be aware of the fact that this
CMS再次意识到以下事实：
is going away and that we very much
正在消失，我们非常
appreciate feedback on d1 and the other
感谢有关d1和其他方面的反馈
collectors help us improve those that's
收藏家可以帮助我们改善那些
that's the future where we want to go
那就是我们要去的未来
the other thing we've done which I think
我认为我们所做的另一件事
effects fewer people is that actually
影响更少的人是，实际上
remove some of the GC combinations that
删除一些GC组合
we have in earlier JD case this is
在早期的JD案例中，这是
something we deprecated in JDK 8 and
我们在JDK 8中弃用了
that we have now removed completely in 9
现在我们已经在9中完全删除了
there used to be something called ICMS
曾经有一个叫做ICMS的东西
and there was also a set of different
而且还有一组不同的
combinations of various DC's that seemed
各种DC的组合似乎
to be not very well used let's say
说不是很好用
were again hard for us to maintain those
再次让我们难以维持
are now gone other stuff we've done to
现在已经走了我们做过的其他事情
improve things both sharing footprint
改善双方共享的足迹
and performance is work on something we
性能是我们工作的基础
call CD s CD s is short for class data
呼叫CD的CD是类数据的缩写
sharing this functionality has been in
共享此功能已在
the JDK for quite some time as well if
JDK也要花相当长的时间
you used to be limited to the Java base
您过去仅限于Java基础
classes the JRE classes themselves but
自己对JRE进行分类，但是
as of I think one of the eight you
截至目前，我认为您八个
updates or eight updates I should say or
更新或八个更新，我应该说或
nine we also now have support for
九，我们现在也支持
application classes as well so this is
应用程序类也是如此
not limited to the GRE anymore it's
不仅限于GRE，
something that you can use for your your
可以用于您的东西的东西
application classes as well and the way
应用程序类以及方法
this effectively works is that you have
这有效地工作是，你有
a sort of training run where you run
一种跑步训练
your application once and what the VM
您的应用程序一次以及什么VM
will do is to read all the classes
要做的就是阅读所有课程
format them and put them in a way that
格式化它们并以某种方式
the JVM likes internally in a more
JVM内部更喜欢
optimized format for the JVM and then
针对JVM的优化格式，然后
store that into what we call the
将其存储到我们所谓的
application class that were CVS archive
CVS存档的应用程序类
for short it's effectively a shared
简而言之，这实际上是一种共享
library much like you defined on the
库非常像您在
operating system level but but but it's
操作系统级别，但它是
not an elf it's not in the native format
不是小精灵，它不是本机格式
of the operating system right now at
现在的操作系统
least and then that's that's your
至少那是你的
training run and then for every run
训练跑步，然后每次跑步
subsequent run you do of the JVM after
随后运行JVM之后
that will point where you can point it
那会指出你可以指出的地方
to these this archive and it will make
这些档案，它将使
use of the information that is in the
使用
archive and leverage that one of the key
存档并利用其中的关键之一
things we've done in 89 year is to
我们在89年中所做的事情是
improve on what is in what goes into the
改善所涉内容
archive so it used to be that it was
存档，所以它曾经是
basically just the class data itself the
基本上只是类数据本身
bytecode and the side structures but now
字节码和侧面结构，但现在
we can also store in turn strings and
我们还可以依次存储字符串和
this is also something that is evolving
这也在不断发展
is where we're looking at adding even
是我们正在考虑添加甚至
more to this going forward you have two
展望未来，您还有两个
major types of improvements here the
主要的改进类型
first one is startup time so by four
第一个是启动时间，所​​以四个
since the VM no longer has to read the
由于VM不再需要读取
class data from file from your jar files
来自jar文件中文件的类数据
for class files and massaged that and
对于班级文件，并按摩和
make sure that it's in the right format
确保格式正确
and again all of that instead now we can
再一次所有这些，现在我们可以
just pick up this shared archive and
只需拿起这个共享档案，
it's already on the right
它已经在右边
you get startup time improvements and in
您可以改善启动时间并
this specific case we're looking at
我们正在研究的这种特定情况
WebLogic server based domain and we can
基于WebLogic服务器的域，我们可以
see that the improvement is ballpark
看到改进是球场
25-30 percent something like that this
像这样的百分之25-30
will clearly vary a bit on your
显然会对您有所不同
application but I think we've seen that
应用程序，但我认为我们已经看到了
typically you'll see this ballpark
通常你会看到这个球场
number 25 30 % and startup time so it's
25 30％和启动时间，所​​以
pretty significant and the other aspect
非常重要，另一方面
of this is footprint so the fact that
这是足迹，所以事实
now more of the data can be shared
现在可以共享更多数据
across instances means that you have
跨实例意味着您拥有
less waste less footprint for the
减少浪费，减少占地面积
individual instances and obviously the
个别实例，显然
more instances you run the better this
您运行的实例越多，效果越好
does assume to some extent that you're
确实在某种程度上假设您是
running similar applications that that
运行类似的应用程序
it's likely the same exact stack of
这可能是相同的确切堆栈
software or at least that they share
软件或至少它们共享
some common frameworks and libraries but
一些常见的框架和库，但是
I think from what we've seen that that's
我认为从我们所看到的
a very typical deployment environment
一个非常典型的部署环境
and I think it's even more common with
我认为这种情况在
environments like doctor where you
像医生这样的环境
actually have the exact same image and
实际上具有完全相同的图像
you stamp out multiple different
您将多个不同
containers from that so the nice part
来自那个的容器，所以很棒的部分
here is that this works together with
这是与
doctor as well as a matter of fact if
医生以及事实是否
you place the the shared archive in a
您将共享档案放在
layer that gets shared across doctor
在医生之间共享的层
containers then it will work very much
容器，那么它将非常有用
like operating system shared libraries
像操作系统共享库
and it may not look like we're saving a
而且看起来好像我们没有保存
lot so the the bars here are the unique
很多，所以这里的酒吧是独一无二的
data per instance with and without app
包含和不包含应用程序的每个实例的数据
serious it's the shared data with and
严重的是与和
without the absolute Lea's and it is the
没有绝对的利亚，这是
total footprint with and without the
有和没有的总占地面积
absolute yes and it may look like the
绝对是的，它看起来像
bars are similar you should note that
酒吧是相似的，你应该注意
the y axis is logarithmic but in the end
y轴是对数的，但最后
this actually does add up over time so
这实际上会随着时间的推移加起来，所以
this is in this case 10 different
在这种情况下，这是10种不同
instances if you run even more you get
实例，如果您运行更多，您将获得
more sharing and what we're seeing here
更多分享以及我们在这里看到的内容
is approximately 10% which may not sound
大约是10％，可能听不到
like a lot for like my laptop but if you
非常喜欢我的笔记本电脑，但如果您
if you stamp that out across a data
如果您将其标记在数据中
center with hundreds of thousands of
拥有数十万个中心
instances then it suddenly starts
实例然后突然开始
turning into real dollars
变成真实的美元
I want to mention that app CDs will be
我想说的是，应用程序CD将是
open sourced this is functionality that
开源这是功能
the CD s aspect has always been open but
CD的方面一直是开放的，但是
the app CD s aspect has been closed but
应用CD的外观已关闭，但
we're working on open sourcing this I
我们正在对此进行开源
cannot promise which exactly release it
无法保证将其完全释放
will go into but suffice to say that we
将进入，但足以说我们
were very eager to get this out so as
非常渴望得到这个
soon as possible
尽快
on the on a similar topic we have AB CD
在类似的主题上，我们有AB CD
s that takes care of Java class data and
负责处理Java类数据和
the other thing we worked on the last
我们在最后工作的另一件事
few years is functionality called
几年被称为功能
alt or ahead of time compilation so this
alt或提前编译，因此
is doing with AB CD with JIT compile the
正在用AB CD和JIT编译
data there were Serge it compiled code
数据有Serge它的编译代码
the same thing that AB CD s does with
AB CD所做的相同的事情
the class data so you know in a normal
班级数据，所以您通常会知道
operating system shared library you have
您拥有的操作系​​统共享库
the data aspect then you have the code
数据方面，那么你有代码
aspect and you package them as a as a
方面，您将它们打包为
live something else probably this is
住别的东西可能是
doing the same thing with code so
用代码做同样的事情
there's a tool called J OTC you give it
有一个叫做J OTC的工具
a class file and it will spit out a
一个类文件，它将吐出一个
shared library in this case it actually
在这种情况下，共享库实际上
is an elf you can't use it apart from in
是一个小精灵，你不能在里面使用它
the VM obviously but it's still stored
VM很明显，但是它仍然被存储
in that exact same format so you you
以完全相同的格式，所以您
basically do again sort of a training
基本上再做一次训练
run but in this case it's a tool that
运行，但在这种情况下，它是一个工具
you run and then for subsequent JVM runs
您运行，然后用于后续的JVM运行
you point it to that shared library and
您将其指向该共享库，
the shared library will be reused the
共享库将被重用
code itself is not as efficient and not
代码本身效率不高
as performant as you would what would
像您一样表现出色
you what you would have with the on line
您将拥有在线上的一切
jet the the cervical pilot we have
喷射我们拥有的宫颈飞行员
inside of the VM but the nice part here
在虚拟机内部，但是这里很棒
is that the code that is stored actually
是实际存储的代码
contains a lot of the information and
包含很多信息
profiling code that is needed to drive
驱动所需的性能分析代码
the optimizations later during runtime
稍后在运行时进行优化
and the server compiler will actually
服务器编译器实际上
kick in and improve on this code on top
加入并改进此代码
of what's in the archive so basically
存档中的内容基本上
you get like the first tier of
你会像第一层
performance using the t code and then
使用äôt代码然后
during runtime will optimize on top of
在运行时将优化
that the functionality is experimental
该功能是实验性的
in 9 and only currently available on
在9中，并且仅在
x64 that said we're adding platform
x64表示我们正在添加平台
support over time and similar types of
随着时间的推移以及类似类型的支持
benefits can be seen from a OT here I am
可以从我的旧约中看到好处
slide on it actually next slide isn't
在它上面滑动实际上不是下一张幻灯片
that so I'll wait with that but you have
那我等一下，但是你有
startup you have time to peak
启动您有时间达到顶峰
performance instead of having to go
性能而不用去
through the full cycle of first
贯穿整个第一周期
interpreting code and then probe
解释代码然后探查
compiling code with profiling capturing
使用性能分析捕获来编译代码
code in it and then optimizing the code
代码，然后优化代码
fully in the end we have already sort of
最终我们已经完全
shortcut the first part of that so you
捷径的第一部分，所以你
have faster time Northshore shorter time
有更快的时间北岸时间更短
to peak performance or reduce time to
达到最佳性能或减少时间
peak performance and the code can
峰值性能和代码可以
obviously also be shared across
显然也可以共享
instances you also get to footprint
实例，您也会涉足
savings in addition to being something
除了成为东西之外还节省
that is useful to end users this is also
对最终用户有用，这也是
something we're planning on using
我们正在计划使用的东西
internally in the JDK to be able to move
在JDK内部可以移动
our JIT compiler up into Java to
我们的JIT编译器转换为Java
implement that in Java instead still
仍然用Java实现
working progress but this is
工作进度，但这是
functionality that is sort of a
有点像
prerequisite for that I won't go into
我不会进入的先决条件
exactly all the details of this slide
这张幻灯片的所有细节
but I will say that it is showing
但我会说它正在显示
basically that you have the default case
基本上你有默认情况
you have the case where you have only a
你有这样的情况，你只有一个
OT you have the case where you have CD s
OT，您有CD的情况
and you have the case where you have
你有情况
both and basically what it's
两者，基本上是什么
highlighting is the fact that they're
突出的事实是，他们
both improving things in themselves but
既可以改善自身状况，又可以
together is where we get the most
在一起是我们最大的收获
benefit out of them
从中受益
so together CD s and alt together is a
所以CD和ALT一起是一个
very happy combination if you want to
如果你想的话，很快乐的组合
know more about a OT it turns out that
知道更多关于OT的事实
we have at least two sessions on that as
我们至少有两次会议
well so again I'll have a slide on this
好吧，我将再次对此进行幻灯片
later at the end of the the presentation
演讲结束后
in case you want to look at it and I'll
万一你想看看，我会
go through the rest of the slides really
仔细浏览其余的幻灯片
quickly I'm sorry for that Java flight
很快，我为那趟Java飞行感到抱歉
recorder I want to highlight that this
录音机，我想强调一点
tool has helped us in term we find a lot
工具帮助我们找到了很多东西
of bottlenecks this is functionality
瓶颈是功能
that captures information in a very
捕获信息非常
fine-grain way but in a very fast and
细粒度的方式，但是速度非常快
efficient way so basically the goal is
有效的方法，所以基本上目标是
to have it default on and always collect
使其默认打开并始终收集
all this data and we also have some
所有这些数据，我们也有一些
visualization help to show that and we
可视化帮助表明这一点，我们
can
能够
we're using this internally to drive
我们在内部使用它来驱动
development JFR is also being open
开发JFR也正在开放
sourced again where we want to try to do
再次在我们想尝试的地方采购
that as quickly as possible but no
尽快，但没有
quicker and if you want to know about
更快，如果您想了解
more about flight recorder or for that
有关飞行记录器的更多信息
sake Mission Control which is the
清酒任务控制是
visualization tool there are sessions on
可视化工具上有会议
that as well and I'll skip through these
同样，我将跳过这些
slides I do want to say that we've
幻灯片，我确实想说我们
unified our login framework we have a
统一我们的登录框架，我们有一个
unified logging framework in the JVM now
现在，JVM中的统一日志记录框架
there used to be like four or ten or
过去大约是四，十或
twenty or something depending on which
二十岁左右
subsystem you had in JVM now we have one
您在JVM中拥有的子系统现在我们有一个
so you can control all the logging using
这样您就可以使用
this one framework and I'm personally
这个框架，我个人
super happy to see that this was a very
很高兴看到这是一个非常
fast snapshot of functionality here are
功能的快速快照如下
other things that went into JDK 9
JDK 9中的其他内容
grouped together and the whole week
和整个星期在一起
obviously you will have a chance to
显然，您将有机会
catch up on these this different these
赶上这些不同的这些
different aspects but hopefully that
不同方面，但希望
gave you a quick insight into the
让您快速了解了
functionality aspect and with that I'm
功能方面，我
handing over to Sandia for the
交给桑迪亚
performance part thanks Michael so last
表演部分感谢迈克尔，最后
couple of years we have contributed to
几年来我们为
and collaborated on many optimizations
并合作进行了许多优化
in open JDK towards Gerry canine so some
在开放的JDK中，朝向Gerry犬
of the key optimizations include the
关键的优化包括
vectorization and has been mad crypto
向量化，并已疯狂加密
and compression acceleration compact
和压缩加速紧凑
strings and the new API support and
字符串和新的API支持以及
optimizing the new API for the Intel
为英特尔优化新的API
platforms so the Intel recently released
平台，所以英特尔最近发布了
skylake platform in july and unless
7月的Skylake平台，除非
otherwise stated most of the performance
除非另有说明
runs are done on the top pin skylake
运行在顶针Skylake
platform that is the Intel Xeon Platinum
平台即英特尔至强白金
8180 at 2.5 gigahertz with turbo at 3.8
8180的2.5千兆赫兹和3.8的涡轮增压
gigahertz so with 384 gb of ram and we
千兆赫兹，所以有384 gb的ram，我们
are comparing the latest JDK 8 release
正在比较最新的JDK 8版本
the JDK 8 update 144 with the JDK 9
使用JDK 9的JDK 8更新144
which is just released September 22nd
刚刚于9月22日发布
all the runs were on
所有的运行都在进行中
on the next platform so on the
在下一个平台上
vectorization enhancements we extended
我们扩展了矢量化功能
the vectorization to 512 bits the JVM
向量化到JVM的512位
Jade as in 38 already supports out of
38岁的Jade已经支持
vectorization they do supervise our
矢量化他们确实监督我们
vector ization so that has been now
向量化，到现在
extended to 512 bits to benefit from the
扩展到512位以受益于
avx-512 that is supported on the Skydeck
Skydeck支持的avx-512
platform we to super unrolling of the
我们超级展开的平台
vectorized main loop there is reduction
向量化的主循环有减少
support is added vector loops with
支持添加了矢量循环
reduction in them are Nova Christ and
他们的减少是新星基督和
also there is support for additional
还支持其他
operations that get vectorized now so
现在可以向量化的操作
I'll go into that details next couple of
我接下来的几个细节
fights
打架
so avx-512 is introduced in the Intel
因此avx-512在Intel中引入
Xeon Phi processor and is available on
至强融核处理器，可用于
the Intel skylake processor it basically
英特尔Skylake处理器
extends
延伸
simply to 512 bit wide that means 64
只需宽到512位，即64
byte operations can be done in a single
字节操作可以一次完成
instruction or 30 to a short 16 in tower
指令或30到简短的16塔
16 single position and 8
16单位置和8
double-precision floating-point
双精度浮点
operations can be done in a single
操作可以一次完成
instruction there are 32 CMM registers
指令有32个CMM寄存器
which are 500 called bit wide so what we
有500个叫位宽，所以我们
have done is to add support for
已经做的就是增加对
cogeneration amick so I went to
热电联产艾米克，所以我去了
cogeneration in the JVM jet and extended
在JVM jet中进行热电联产并扩展
the similar vectorization we have also
我们也有类似的向量化
optimized the array string intrinsic
优化数组字符串固有
methods to benefit from avx-512 so this
受益于AVX-512的方法
is a small Java example that we have
是一个小的Java示例
shown that we have used to show the
表明我们曾经展示过
benefit between Gerry cage
格里笼之间的好处
nine this the loop colonel does get auto
九这个循环上校确实自动
vectorized here there is the operation
向量化这里有操作
being done on elements of two arrays and
在两个数组的元素上完成
the result is stored in a third array so
结果存储在第三个数组中
this particular example with different
这个特殊的例子与众不同
data types and different operations is
数据类型和不同的操作是
what we showed to ensure the benefit so
我们为确保收益而展示的
the we are basically comparing the 32
我们基本上是比较32
byte vectorization that was available on
字节向量化
the previous platforms to 64 byte that
以前的平台要64字节
is 512 bit Elektra ization that's now
现在是512位Elektra
available in geni k9 you need to use the
在geni k9中可用，您需要使用
use of X equal to 3 JVM command line
使用X等于3个JVM命令行
option to get 512 bit Twitter ization
选择获得512位Twitter认证
and we also show the benefit of
而且我们也展示了
alignment JVM has an option called optic
对齐JVM有一个称为Optical的选项
alignment in pipes which you can use to
可以在管道中对齐
align the data type so this chart here
对齐数据类型，因此此图表在此处
shows the performance gain for
显示了的性能提升
floating-point operation from 32 byte
从32字节开始的浮点运算
vector to 64 byte vector and the
向量到64字节向量和
performance gain is up to 30 percent
性能提升高达30％
without alignment and goes up to 70
没有对齐并且上升到70
percent with alignment and here we show
对齐的百分比，这里我们显示
the performance of integer arithmetic
整数运算的性能
and logical operations here the
和逻辑运算在这里
performance gain is up to 40 percent
性能提升高达40％
without alignment and 80 percent with
没有对齐和80％
alignment so the auto vectorization not
对齐，因此自动矢量化不会
only benefits the classic Java code but
仅有益于经典Java代码，但
it also helps streams that was
它也可以帮助
introduced in G decade so okay there is
在G十年中引入，所以还可以
a lambda somewhat more complex
一个更复杂的lambda
expression than the previous example
表达式比上一个示例
and this lambda gets Auto vectorized and
这个lambda会自动矢量化
if you would have used parallel along
如果您会使用平行
with this this lambda then you would see
有了这个lambda，那么你会看到
again a cross multi-core and as well as
再次跨多核以及
you'll benefit from the vector unit on
您将受益于
the processor so here this run is done
处理器，所以这里运行完成
on a single code and you see there's a
在单个代码上，您会看到有一个
gain up to 60% with alignment and 64
对准和64可获得高达60％的增益
byte vector so as I mentioned before
字节向量，就像我之前提到的
jelly canine has vectorization and has
果冻犬具有矢量化功能并具有
made over JDK 8 so in dedicate given a
通过JDK 8制作，因此专用于
simple loop like I showed in the
就像我在
previous example the there is a pre loop
前面的例子有一个前循环
main loop and the post loop generated
主循环和后循环生成
the pre loop does the destination
前循环执行目标
alignment and the main loop is the one
对齐和主循环是一个
that gets auto vectorized and the scalar
自动矢量化和标量
post loop is for tail processing so in
后循环用于尾部处理，因此
jdk 9 we now super unroll the vector
jdk 9我们现在超级展开向量
main loop since the vector main loop a
自向量主循环以来的主循环
super unroll there is a vector single
超级展开有一个向量单
iteration post loop which can do as much
迭代后循环可以做很多事情
operation remaining operation using
操作剩余操作使用
vector instructions as possible
尽可能的矢量指令
so here is an example of reduction so
所以这是减少的一个例子
the highlighted portion of the code is
代码的突出显示部分是
doing the sum reduction of
进行总和减少
multiplication of area elements and
面积元素的乘积和
prior to JDK 9 reduction was not
减少JDK 9之前
supported basically if there was such a
基本支持如果有这样的
reduction in a classic Java code the
减少经典的Java代码
loop won't get vectorized and you won't
循环不会被矢量化，您也不会
see benefit from vectorization angelica
受益于矢量化当归
9 and the reduction is supported and you
9并且支持减少，您
can see that up to 2x gain is seen for
可以看到，最高可获得2倍的增益
this particular code here I show the
这个特定的代码我在这里显示
vector post loop to generated code and I
向量后循环生成的代码和我
can see that the multiplication VP ml LD
可以看到乘法VP ml LD
that is a vector instruction and the
这是向量指令，
rest of the code is for the summation
其余代码用于求和
the reduction operation and summation is
归约运算和求和为
used extensively for example in
广泛用于例如
convolution for image processing or
卷积进行图像处理或
k-means algorithm matrix multiplication
k-均值算法矩阵乘法
so those all can get now out of a closed
这样所有的人都可以从封闭中走出来
so we also recognized additional
所以我们也认识到
expressions in the vector loop and
向量循环中的表达式和
basically vectorize the loop for example
例如，基本上将循环向量化
the math dot square root if there is a
数学点平方根（如果有）
square root performed on every element
对每个元素执行平方根
of the array that now gets recognized
现在被识别的阵列
and we generate a vector square root
然后生成向量平方根
instruction there we square root PV and
那里的说明，我们平方根PV和
you can see going from dedicate to JDK 9
您可以看到从专用转向JDK 9
we see about greater than 5x performance
我们看到性能提高了5倍以上
for this loop
对于这个循环
so in Cherokee 9 there's another feature
所以在切诺基9中还有另一个功能
introduced called compact strings so for
引入了所谓的紧凑型琴弦
this we collaborated with the Oracle
我们与甲骨文合作
charlie hunt dimension Tobias Hartman
查理·亨特维度Tobias Hartman
and many others so basically what
还有很多其他的东西
compact string does is it tries to use
紧凑的字符串会尝试使用吗
one byte storage for characters of a
一个字节存储一个字符
string in Java by default it supports
Java默认支持的字符串
the Unicode characters that is there are
那里的Unicode字符
two bytes per character but s key and
每个字符两个字节，但s键和
English the upper body is always zero so
英语上半身总是零
you can use single byte for characters
您可以使用单字节字符
so without changing what's visible to
因此，无需更改可见内容
the user internally the internal storage
用户内部存储
is changed from character array to a
从字符数组更改为
byte array and if all the elements of
字节数组，如果所有元素
the string fit within a byte then the
字符串适合一个字节，然后
string elements are stored in a single
字符串元素存储在单个
bytes and if not the string is inflated
字节，如果不是，则字符串被夸大
and two pipes are used for element so
和两个管道用于元素所以
what this does is strings are
这是字符串
extensively used in any of the Java
广泛用于任何Java
programs so it reduces the underlying
程序，这样可以减少底层
storage that is used by the program and
该程序使用的存储和
not only that most of the interesting
不仅最有趣
operations are done at the back using
操作在后面使用
vector instructions so now because the
矢量指令，所以现在因为
string is the string elements are half
字符串是字符串元素的一半
the size you can do double the
你可以做一倍的大小
operations behind so so there is a
操作背后，所以有一个
performance improvement is also possible
性能改善也是可能的
there is some overhead to check each
有一些开销来检查每个
element and inflate the string if
元素，并在字符串增加时
possible so both this the the memory
可能，所以这两个内存
size which improves the garbage
改善垃圾的大小
collection performance and the ability
收集性能和能力
to do double the operation is benefit to
做两倍的手术对
the applications
应用程序
here this is an example we had run
这是我们运行的一个例子
spectively be 2005 this one was done
分别在2005年完成了
on'y has well a desktop and this is a
on'y的桌面非常好，这是一个
peak run so we saw about 5% performance
高峰运行，所以我们看到了大约5％的效果
improvement in the peak throughput first
首先提高峰值吞吐量
picture baby 2005 and this is a heap
图片宝贝2005，这是一个堆
dump so you can see that the the total
转储，这样您就可以看到总数
number of objects instances is about
实例数量约
similar between JDK 8 and JDK 9 the
JDK 8和JDK 9之间的相似之处
number of bytes that is used is reduced
减少了使用的字节数
by 20% and if you see the highlighted
减少20％，如果您看到突出显示的内容
portion which is showing the number of
显示数字的部分
instances of character array and the
字符数组和
number of instances of byte array so
字节数组的实例数，因此
whatever was character array before is
以前的字符数组是
now by today with JDK 9 so angelica 9 we
现在通过JDK 9到今天，当归9我们
also worked on optimizing the math
还致力于优化数学
library some of the key trigonometric a
库一些关键的三角函数
transcendental methods like the sine
正弦等先验方法
cost an exponential and log they were
花费了指数并记录了
optimized and you can see gain up to 5x
优化，您可以看到高达5倍的增益
for this math libraries these math
对于这个数学库，这些数学
libraries are extensively used in big
图书馆广泛用于大型
data machine learning the financial of
数据机器学习的财务
option pricing algorithms and HPC and
期权定价算法和HPC以及
here we show three micros for financial
这里我们展示了金融的三个微观指标
option pricing the Monte Carlo box meter
期权定价的蒙特卡洛盒式电表
and black Scholes and they see gain up
和黑人斯科尔斯，他们看到了收获
to 5x and for example and these are
到5倍，例如，这些是
Gotham see use cos sine log square root
哥谭看到使用cos正弦对数平方根
power exp etc that's why the game
power exp等，这就是游戏的原因
JDK nine
JDK九
we also worked on optimizing the key
我们还致力于优化密钥
crypto algorithms to benefit from the
加密算法可从中受益
internal architecture instruction so
内部架构说明
Intel Architecture provides in yes and I
英特尔架构提供了是和我
catalyst multiplied and you know avx2
催化剂倍增，您知道avx2
also you can do 64-bit multiplies and
你也可以做64位乘法
get 128-bit result
获得128位结果
so all that used at the back in the in
所以所有在后面的东西
the optimized dubs benefits the the
优化的配音有益于
crypto Java provides all the crypto
加密Java提供所有加密
through a provider framework the Java
通过提供程序框架Java
cryptography architecture and sunjai C
密码体系结构和Sunjai C
is the default provider so we have
是默认提供程序，所以我们有
optimized the Sun JC provider methods
优化了Sun JC提供程序方法
through optimized ups and you can see up
通过优化的ups，您可以看到
to 10x gain for a yes counter and a yes
计数器的收益是10倍
GCM decode so the the SHA optimization
GCM解码，因此SHA优化
here is through the AVX instructions the
这是通过AVX指令
AES counter and the AES GCM his
AES计数器和AES GCM
expressions are three a yes and I GCM
表达式是三个，是的，我是GCM
also has a G hash component that
也有一个G哈希组件
benefits from the catalyst multiplied
催化剂的好处成倍增加
and the crypto RSA is through 64-bit
加密RSA通过64位
multiply giving a 128-bit result at the
乘以给出128位结果
ADC X 80 or accessories so JDK nine for
ADC X 80或附件，因此JDK 9
compression acceleration JDK nine also
压缩加速JDK九还
added a feature prior to Cherokee nine
在切诺基九之前添加了功能
interrogate the the sealy was bundled a
审讯被捆绑的大海
lot as part of the lip zipped or so so
很多作为嘴唇的一部分拉链左右
now in jdk nine uses the system Celebi
现在在jdk九使用Celebi系统
instead of the bundle select so that
而不是选择束，这样
gives the capability to the user to
使用户有能力
replace the systems you live with the
用
software accelerated were not a hardware
加速的软件不是硬件
accelerated
加速的
one and here I have given two links the
一个，在这里我给了两个链接
software acceleration can be done either
可以进行软件加速
through the Intel performance primitives
通过英特尔性能原语
or there is a github project which is
或者有一个github项目是
listed in the document here that could
在此处列出的文件中
be used and for hardware acceleration in
用于硬件加速
Intel introduced quick assist as part of
英特尔推出了快速协助，将其作为
the skylake the chipset Louisburg
天际芯片组路易斯堡
chipset so the quick assist also has
芯片组，因此快速协助也有
compression acceleration capability
压缩加速能力
through a driver and the library support
通过驱动程序和库支持
that can be found at the link given him
可以在给他的链接中找到
so this this one shows the performance
所以这个这个显示了性能
improvement through software
通过软件改进
acceleration I used open source the leap
我用开源加速了飞跃
from the link given here and the
从这里给出的链接和
performance shown is for the Calgary
显示的性能是针对卡尔加里的
corpus data set the compression portion
语料库数据设置压缩部分
and the only thing I had to do was to
我唯一要做的就是
get the source code built a library and
获取源代码，构建一个库，然后
set the LD library path to the built
将LD库路径设置为已构建
library and we can see em you know 1.5 X
库，我们可以看到您知道1.5 X
2 up to 3x gain in compression so that
2高达3倍的压缩增益，因此
was very encouraging stuff on Freebird
在Freebird上非常令人鼓舞的东西
added the crc32 C to Java 9 and Intel
在Java 9和Intel中添加了crc32 C
has the instruction called crc32 C which
的指令称为crc32 C
can be used to implement the crc32 C of
可用于实现crc32 C的
the Java 9 API and this is the basically
Java 9 API，这基本上是
the I scuzzy CRC polynomial and prior to
我对CRC多项式模糊不清
JDK 9 and in dedicate as well as
JDK 9以及专用
Cherokee 9 both have the Joey tells if
切诺基9都有乔伊告诉
crc32 which is a different the CRC
crc32与CRC不同
polynomial and and that was the the JIT
多项式，那就是JIT
zip crc32 is optimized using the
zip crc32使用
catalyst multiplied so the crc32 see the
催化剂成倍增加，因此crc32参见
new API gives an additional 2x
新的API增加了2倍
performance improvement over a
性能改善
previously optimized version so and we
以前的优化版本，所以我们
know that the checksum is extensively
知道校验和是广泛的
used wherever there is a lot of data for
用于有大量数据的地方
example Cassandra HBase they all use the
示例Cassandra HBase，它们都使用
checksum API in lexicographic array
字典数组中的校验和API
comparison was introduced by Paul
比较由保罗介绍
Sanders and we worked closely with Paul
桑德斯，我们与保罗紧密合作
Sanders to optimize the area compare
桑德斯优化面积比较
using the same D instructions at the
使用相同的D指令
back and array compare is used in
返回和数组比较用于
Cassandra and HBase for key comparison
Cassandra和HBase进行关键比较
so for example Cassandra uses blocks of
例如，Cassandra使用
size 8 K or 64 K so you know and there
大小为8 K或64 K，所以您知道那里
is a checksum calculated for each block
是为每个块计算的校验和
so this is going to benefit that and we
所以这将使我们受益
have the underlying algorithm a team is
有一个团队的基础算法
using the similar instructions
使用类似的指示
and last but not the least there was an
最后但并非最不重要的一点是
MMA API added by Joe Darcy which does
由Joe Darcy添加的MMA API
the multiplication and addition and
乘法和加法以及
after addition the truncation part has
添加后，截断部分具有
turned after addition so Java spec does
加法后打开，因此Java规范会
not allow us to you know optimize if
不允许我们知道优化
there is a multiplication and addition
有一个乘法和加法
we can't optimize that using FME because
我们无法使用FME对其进行优化，因为
it expects us to do the the rounding or
它希望我们进行四舍五入或
the truncation part after each operation
每次操作后的截断部分
so with this new API now we can optimize
所以现在有了这个新的API，我们可以优化
FME using the underlying architecture as
FME使用基础架构作为
affirming instruction and FMA is used in
确认说明和FMA用于
convolution for image processing it is
卷积的图像处理是
used in matrix multiplication in class
用于类的矩阵乘法
algorithms so this is beneficial for HPC
算法，因此对HPC有利
and machine learning so yeah I think
和机器学习，是的，我认为
what others have shown a lot of new
其他人展示了很多新东西
features that are available in j9 so
在j9中可用的功能
please download it try it out and give
请下载并试用并给出
us feedback and this is the legal
我们的反馈，这是合法的
disclaimer and optimization notice from
的免责声明和优化通知
Intel
英特尔
[Applause]
[掌声]